DDoS in the IoT: Mirai and other botnets
Kolias, Constantinos and Kambourakis, Georgios and Stavrou, Angelos and Voas, Jeffrey
The ubiquity and increasing popularity of the In à ôTHE FUTUREö IS HERE A recent prominent 
example is the Mirai botnet. First iden- tified in August 2016 by the whitehat security research 
group MalwareMustDie,1 MiraiùJapanese for ôthe futureöùand its many variants and imitators à
N-BaIoTùNetwork-based detection of IoT botnet attacks using deep autoencoders
Meidan, Yair and Bohadana, Michael and Mathov, Yael and Mirsky, Yisroel and Shabtai, Asaf and Breitenbacher, Dominik and Elovici, Yuval
The proliferation of IoT devices that can be more easily compromised than desktop computers has led to an increase in IoT-based botnet attacks. To mitigate this threat, there is a need for new methods that detect attacks launched from compromised IoT devices and à
Botnets and internet of things security
Bertino, Elisa and Islam, Nayeem
à SECTION TITLE CYBERTRUST The large number of insecure Internet of Things (IoT) devices
with high computation power make them an easy and attractive target for attackers seeking to
compromise these devices and use them to create large-scale botnets. A botnet is a à 

